Treasure never stays buried for long.
Low Tide is a thriller film directed by Kevin McMullin.
In the long days of summer in a beach town on the New Jersey shore, high schooler Alan and his friends Red and Smitty
break into vacation homes to steal valuables, funding dates at the boardwalk and lunches at the burger stand.
When Alan and his younger brother Peter find a bag of gold coins, they try to hide them from the others — but
Red, suspicious and violently unpredictable, seems willing to do anything to get the money.
Peter, played by Jaeden Martell.
Alan, played by Keean Johnson.
Sergeant Kent, played by Shea Whigham.
Red, played by Alex Neustaedter.
Smitty, played by Daniel Zolghadri.
Mary, played by Kristine Froseth.
Low Tide is a 2019 American drama film, written and directed by Kevin McMullin.
It stars Keean Johnson, Alex Neustaedter, Daniel Zolghadri,
Kristine Froseth, Shea Whigham, and Jaeden Martell.
It had its world premiere at the Tribeca Film Festival on April 28, 2019 and was theatrically released in
the United States on October 4, 2019, by A24 and released internationally by DirecTV Cinema.
The film explores themes of new jersey, boat,
fireworks, stolen money, coming of age.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.